wendyshow.com 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy - The Wendy Williams Show

This Privacy Policy applies only to www.wendyshow.com (however accessed and/or used, whether via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise), which is owned or controlled by Talk WW Production, Inc., dba “The Wendy Williams Show,” its parent, subsidiaries, affiliates, successors and assigns (collectively, “Company,” “we,” “our” or “us”), or other interactive features that are accessible or downloadable through www.wendyshow.com (excluding any third party web sites) and that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Web Site”). This Privacy Policy only covers information collected at the Web Site, and does not cover any information collected at any other web site or offline by Company (unless specifically stated).  
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. Company provides this Privacy Policy to help you make an informed decision about whether to use or continue using our Web Site. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect on the Web Site, how we may use and collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you may have regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of such information.  
This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time, so please revisit this page to remain fully informed of our privacy policy. In addition, this Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is subject to our Terms of Use which govern your use of the Web Site and the content you submit to the Web Site and any separate guidelines document or end user license agreement setting forth additional conditions may apply to a service or feature offered through this Web Site (“Additional Terms”).

## TABLE OF CONTENTS

  * Types Of Information We Collect:
    * Information You Provide Us
    * Information From Other Sources
    * Cookies
    * Web Beacons
  * How We Use The Information We Collect:
  * When We Disclose Information We Collect
  * With Whom We May Share Information
    * Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf
    * When You Agree to Receive Offers From Third Parties
    * Sweepstakes, Contest, Promotions & Giveaways
    * Newsletter
    * Business Transfers
    * Legal Protection and Law Enforcement
    * User Forums
  * Correcting/Updating Personal Information; Cancelling Subscriptions
  * Registering and Obtaining Tickets
  * Third Party Advertisers and Links To Other Web Sites
  * International Users
  * Security
  * Children’s Privacy
  * California Privacy Rights
  * Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy
  * Your rights
  * Retention
  * Contact Information

## Types Of Information That Company May Collect; How We May Collect It

### Information You Provide Us

We may ask you to provide us with two types of information that allows us to deliver you the optimal experience on our site. They include : (1) personal information, which is information that could reasonably be used to identify you personally, such as your name, e-mail address, internet protocol (IP) address, telephone number, cellular telephone number and physical address, as well as any billing information that you may provide to us in connection with any orders or purchases made through the Web Site, such as a credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address; and (2) demographic information such as gender, age, zip code, or current photograph . We may collect this information at various places and forms on the Web Site, including registration forms for tickets, newsletters and other communications (e.g., whether by e-mail, mobile device, etc.); when you communicate or otherwise interact with us in any way including comments, when you request show tickets; when you submit information to us (whether or not the information is intended to be posted on the Web Site); when you enter or participate in contests or sweepstakes, giveaways, surveys or voting; or when you purchase a product or service through the Web Site. You may also be asked to choose a user name and password in order to identify yourself during future visits to the Web Site. **Do not use your real name or the name of any other actual person as your user name. Providing us with information about yourself is your choice. It is your right to choose not to provide certain information** (for example your street address, name, email address, phone number, photo, and IP address) but then you may not be able to take advantage of some of the Web Site’s features such as a subscription to the newsletter or to reserve tickets to the show.

In addition, the Web Site may include forums, message boards, chat rooms, online diaries, social networking areas, or other interactive areas on the Web Site (“User Forums”) available to its users. **If you post personal information online in a User Forum, it will be publicly available and will not be considered personal information for purposes of this Privacy Policy as explained further below. If you feel that the language used in the comment section violates Company’s Terms of Use in any way, specifically if it constitutes harassment, stalking, sexual or violent exploitation, please contact[productionattorney@wendyshow.com](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com).**

### Information from Other Sources

We also may receive information about you from other sources. For example, we may obtain geographic or demographic information, or information regarding your possible interests, from third parties, or we may receive information from a marketing partner in connection with a co-branded web site or promotion. We use this information to enhance our ability to serve you with content and ads in a more personally tailored way. We may combine the information we receive from those other sources with information we collect through the Web Site. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to any personal information received, unless otherwise specifically disclosed by us at the time you provide your personal information.

Please note that we may not respond to questions or information submitted to the Web Site via “Ask Wendy,” “Ticket Request,” “Comments,” or other similar mechanisms, or through third party web sites, such as “Facebook,” “Instagram” or “Twitter.” However, we may contact you regarding your submission or to be a guest on The Wendy Williams Show or www.wendyshow.com. Questions or other information submitted to the Web Site via “Ask Wendy,” “Ticket Request,” “Comments,” or other similar mechanisms, or through third party web sites, such as “Facebook,” “Instagram” or “Twitter,” may be used for broadcast in/on The Wendy Williams Show or on www.wendyshow.com and other web sites used to promote the show and site worldwide in perpetuity without further notice to you or your consent. Pictures submitted by you on “Ticket Request” may be used internally by Company in connection with “The Wendy Williams Show,” You may, however, exercise your right to deletion by reaching out to our Production Attorney at [productionattorney@wendyshow.com](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com). More information on your rights and how to exercise them are included in the Your Rights section below.

 **Cookies: For more information about what cookies are, which cookies we use, and how to further understand and control cookies, please see our Cookie Policy.**

 **What are cookies?** The Web Site uses standard technology called “cookies” which are small data files or strings of text that are transferred to your computer (or other Internet-accessing device) when you visit the Web Site and allow your browser to accept cookies. Cookies automatically identify your web browser to the Web Site whenever you visit the Web Site and may make navigating and using the Web Site easier for you. Additionally, accepting cookies may allow you to, among other things, personalize your experience on the Web Site.

 **Web Beacons:**

The Web Site and any communications sent by the Web Site may contain electronic files or images (generally, single-pixel “.gif” or images) called “web beacons” that allow the Web Site to count users who have visited that page or to access certain cookies. These web beacons allow Company and third parties to monitor and collect certain information about the viewer of the web page, web-based document, e-mail message, or other communication, such as the type of browser requesting the web beacon, the device identifier of the device that the web beacon is sent to and the time the web beacon was viewed.

### How We Use The Information We Collect:

We may use all of the information that we collect to:

  * Send you newsletters and/or other communications for which you have registered;
  * Contact you about the Web Site, including, without limitation, in our discretion to notify you of changes to this Privacy Policy, the Web Site’s Terms of Use, or other policies that affect your use of the Web Site;
  * Provide special offers or promotional materials to you on behalf of us or third parties;
  * Contact you with regard to a giveaway, sweepstakes, contest or promotion in which you have participated and to track your entries in such giveaways, sweepstakes, contests or promotions;
  * Authorize a purchase or complete a transaction that you have requested, or otherwise confirm or fulfill an order you have made (i.e., to deliver the products or other services that you ordered, and, if necessary, to invoice you);
  * Monitor or improve the quality, design, functionality of the Web Site;
  * Administer the Web Site’s systems and for other internal business purposes;
  * Customize the advertising and content you see and to otherwise personalize your experience on the Web Site;
  * Comply with and monitor compliance with our Terms of Use and other applicable agreements and polices;
  * Evaluate you for a possible invitation to be a guest on The Wendy Williams Show or www.wendyshow.com;
  * Generate topics for The Wendy Williams Show or www.wendyshow.com; and
  * For other purposes disclosed when you provide your information.

We may also use the information we collect through the use of cookies and/or web beacons to:

  * monitor metrics such as unique users (actually, unique web browsers), visits and page views;
  * monitor traffic and conversion patterns through our various product and service offerings on the Web Site (for example, web beacons may be integrated into a merchandise product page as well as the subsequent shopping cart, transaction and verification pages);
  * monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; and
  * determine whether or not messages were opened, links were clicked or notifications/offers were acted upon

Moreover, if you submit to Company and/or the Web Site, either through the Web Site or through a third party web site where Company maintains a related content web page(s) (such as, for example and not by way of limitation, on a “Wendy Williams Show” page on a social networking site), comments, photographs, videos (including web cam videos), music, text or other content, then we may publish such submissions online or offline (including via Internet, radio, television, CD, DVD, wireless distribution, and in any other media or format currently existing or hereafter developed), and we may publish your name, voice, likeness and other personal information in connection with publishing the content or a portion of the content. In addition, we may use such submissions and any excerpt from such submissions in connection with advertising, marketing, publicity and promotional activities. Please also see “Information You Submit” in our Terms of Use and any applicable Additional Terms.

## When We Disclose The Information We Collect

 **With Whom We May Share Information:**

We do not share your personal information with third parties for those third parties’ marketing purposes unless you opt-in to such sharing at the time you provide your personal information. We may share non-personal information, such as anonymized aggregate user statistics, demographic information, and web site usage information with third parties. In addition, we may share your information as disclosed at the time you provide your information, as set forth in this Privacy Policy and in the circumstances described below.

 **Third parties providing services on our behalf:**

We employ third parties to perform functions on our behalf; examples include hosting or operating the Web Site, sending e-mail and/or other communications, providing wireless services, removing repetitive information from customer lists, data analysis, marketing assistance, and customer service. These third parties may have access to information collected by Company, including without limitation your personal information, for the purpose of performing such functions on the Web Site’s behalf.

 **When You Agree To Receive Offers From Third Parties:**

Third party(s) may present you with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers. If you do not agree to have your personal information shared, we will not share your personal information with such third party(s) for direct marketing purposes. If you do agree to have your personal information shared, then we will disclose your relevant personal information to such third party(s). All information we disclose as well as all information you provide directly to such third party(s) will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of such third party(s). We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) and, therefore, you should review the privacy policies and practices of such third party(s) prior to agreeing to receive communications from such third party(s) and prior to agreeing disclose such information to such third party(s). If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communication from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly.

 **Sweepstakes, Contests, Promotions and Giveaways:**

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, promotions, and other giveaways through the Web Site that may require registration. If you choose to enter a sweepstakes, contest, promotion or other giveaways, we may disclose your personal information to third parties in connection with the administration of such promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law, such as on a winners list. Also, by entering a promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the promotion to use your name, voice and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the promotion. We may also share your personal information with any third party Prize Sponsor or Prize Administrator who will be assisting with administration of the sweepstakes, contest, promotion or other giveaway of fulfilling its Prize.

 **Newsletter:**

Our Newsletters are periodically sent to users who have previously registered to receive such material. The information obtained during registration (e.g. email address) is securely stored to achieve a more tailored relationship with Company. E-mails given for this purpose are only used for this purpose. At any time, user can “unsubscribe” to this service using the hyperlink at the bottom of any of the e-mails received.

 **Business Transfers:**

Company shares the information collected through the Web Site with and among its parent, subsidiaries and affiliates. Company may sell any of it’s assets, including the Web Site, or consummate other transactions in which your personal information is one of the key business assets for the transaction. In such a case, we may transfer your personal information as one of the business assets we transfer. Hence, Company reserves the right to disclose and transfer user information, including personal information, in connection with a sale of a majority interest in the equity of Company, a corporate merger, consolidation, or restructuring of Company, the sale of all or substantially all of our assets, or other corporate change of Company.

 **Legal Protections and Law Enforcement:**

We may disclose information about our users, including your personal information, in the event we are required to respond to subpoenas, court orders, legal process or other valid law enforcement measures; to comply with a legal obligation; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing the Web Site and applicable laws; or to protect the legal rights, interests, or safety of the Web Site, our users or others. We may also use device identifiers to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers or law enforcement agencies in our discretion. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

Company also reserves the right to disclose personal information and/or non-personal information that Company believes, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend itself against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, to protect the security or integrity of our Web Site, and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Company, our users or others.

 **User Forums:**

The Web Site may make User Forums available to its users or provide links to other third party web sites where Company maintains a related content web page(s) which may include forums, message boards, chat rooms, online diaries, social networking areas, or other interactive areas (“Third Party User Forums”). If you post comments, photographs, videos (including web cam videos), music, text or other content on any User Forums or Third Party User Forums, whether or not such postings include personal information, they will be publicly available (except in certain circumstances, such as “non-shared” user diaries) and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a User Forum or Third Party User Forum. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these areas. Your use of User Forums is at your own risk and is subject to our Terms of Use and any applicable Additional Terms. Your use of Third Party User Forums is subject to such third party’s privacy policy and terms of use. To the extent User has any issues or concerns with Third Party User Forums, User should direct all inquiries and complaints to the appropriate Third Party.

 **Correcting/Updating Personal Information; Cancelling Subscriptions** **:**

The Web Site may contain web pages through which you can correct or update some of the personal information you have provided to us through registration with the Web Site. With regard to subscriptions, you also may cancel (or modify, if applicable) your subscriptions by following the instructions provided to you in applicable communications regarding such subscriptions.

 **Registering and Obtaining Tickets** **:**

BY REGISTERING AND OBTAINING TICKETS TO “THE WENDY WILLIAMS SHOW,” YOU CONSENT TO BE PHOTOGRAPHED BY MEANS OF VIDEO RECORDING AND YOU GRANT THE PRODUCER OF THE FOOTAGE, ITS SUCCESSORS, ASSIGNS, CARRIER STATIONS, NETWORK STATION(S), SPONSOR(S) OF THE PROGRAM AND MARKETING AND ADVERTISING AGENTS (AS WELL AS THEIR AFFILIATED AND RELATED ENTITIES) THE RIGHT TO RECORD AND USE YOUR NAME, VOICE, AND LIKENESS WORLDWIDE IN PERPETUITY FOR ANY PURPOSE WHATSOEVER. IN ADDITION, YOU RELEASE THE ABOVE PARTIES FROM ANY AND ALL LIABILITY FOR LOSS OF DAMAGE TO YOUR PERSON OR PROPERTY WHILE AT OR AROUND THE PREMISES, AND YOU AGREE TO COMPLY WITH ALL RULES AND REGULATIONS OF COMPANY, THE PRODUCER AND THEIR RESPECTIVE AFFILIATES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DEBMAR-MERCURY LLC AND LIONS GATE ENTERTAINMENT CORP.

 **Third-party Advertisers and Links to Other Sites** **:**

We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Web Site. For example, if you “click” on a banner advertisement, the “click” may take you off the Web Site onto a different web site. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use the Web Site’s logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use some of your data to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links personalized for you that appear on the Web Site. In the process of doing this, they receive your IP address. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content you see.

We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Company to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, women ages 18-34) or audience segment (for example, women ages 18-24 who have viewed certain channels of content) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach. The advertiser may also use information regarding your use of the Web Site, such as the number of times you viewed an ad through your cookies (but not any personally identifiable information), to determine which ads to deliver to you.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with our Company is maintained and dealt with by Company in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

 **International Users:**

The Web Site is hosted in the United States and is intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are a user accessing the Web Site from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Web Site, which is governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Policy, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

 **Security** **:**

Company uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure, warrant or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to Company and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Company makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.

If Company learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Company may post a notice on the Web Site if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify us at [productionattorney@wendyshow.com ](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com%C2%A0). ** **

 **Children’s Privacy** **:**

The Web Site is a general audience web site. Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. We recognize the importance of safeguarding the privacy of children and encourage parents to check and monitor their children’s use of online activities regularly. The Web Site supports and complies with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) and other laws. The Web Site is not aimed at nor intended for children under the age of 13 and we will delete any information later determined to be from a user younger than thirteen (13). If you are under the age of 13, please do not use the Web Site. Our Web Site does not accept registration from children under the age of 13. No personally identifiable information (as defined in the COPPA, 15 U.S.C. Section 6501) is purposefully or knowingly collected from children under the age of 13 by Company on the Web Site without parental consent. Every user hereby agrees that all information you provide, including but not limited to age, shall be truthful and correct. Company will not condition a child’s participation in an online activity on the child providing more personally identifiable information than is reasonably necessary for participation in such activity.

 **California Privacy Rights** **:**

A California resident who has provided personal information to a business with whom he/she has established a business relationship for personal, family, or household purposes (“California customer”) is entitled to request information about whether the business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. In general, if the business has made such a disclosure of personal information, upon receipt of a request by a California customer, the business is required to provide a list of all third parties to whom personal information was disclosed in the preceding calendar year, as well as a list of the categories of personal information that were disclosed.

However, under the law, a business is not required to provide the above-described information if the business adopts and discloses to the public (in its privacy policy) a policy of not disclosing customer’s personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless the customer first affirmatively agrees to the disclosure, as long as the business maintains and discloses this policy. Rather, the business may comply with the law by notifying the customer of his or her right to prevent disclosure of personal information and providing a cost free means to exercise that right.

As stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not share information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes unless you affirmatively agree to such disclosure — typically by opting in to receive information from a third party that is participating in a sweepstakes or other promotion on one of our sites. To prevent disclosure of your personal information for use in direct marketing by a third party, do not opt in to such use when you provide personally identifiable information on the Web Site. Please note that whenever you opt in to receive future communications from a third party, your information will be subject to the third party’s privacy policy. If you later decide that you do not want that third party to use your information, you will need to contact the third party directly, as we have no control over how third parties use information. You should always review the privacy policy of any party that collects your information to determine how that entity will handle your information.

California consumers may direct requests for a copy of the specific personal information  by e-mail to [productionattorney@wendyshow.com](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com). Please note that we are only obligated to respond to two requests each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address.

 **Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy** **:**

By using the Web Site, you acknowledge your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. From time to time, Company may update this Privacy Policy. Company will use your personal information in a manner consistent with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time you submitted the information, unless you consent to the new or revised policy. Your continued use of the Web Site constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Policy and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Policy that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of the personal information you have already provided to us, we will attempt to obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

 **Your Rights** **:**

You have various rights in relation to your personal data, including:

  * the right to request information regarding how your personal data is processed;
  * the right to have your personal data rectified if inaccurate or out of date;
  * the right to have your personal data erased in certain limited circumstances;
  * the right to object to certain processing or to have certain processing restricted;
  * the right to have your personal data transferred from one data controller to another; and
  * the right to lodge a complaint with your nation’s data protection regulator or the appropriate legal body within your country.

If you have any questions about these rights, please contact us at [productionattorney@wendyshow.com](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com) or your country’s information protection agency. Please note, these rights are not absolute and there may be conditions which must be met before you can enforce these rights.

 **Retention** **:**

The information we collect and maintain directly from you are stored on the servers of service providers that allow us to give you the best possible website experience. The pieces of information you provide when commenting, requesting tickets, or enter information for any other reason are stored on our servers for no longer than necessary in order to give you the best experience and are deleted after it no longer serves you a use. We may keep certain contact information such as information provided by you in your initial ticket request in order to allow us to get back in touch with you for additional opportunities to attend the show.

 **Contact Information** **:**

Please email the Production Attorney at [productionattorney@wendyshow.com](mailto:productionattorney@wendyshow.com) _w_ ith any questions, comments, or concerns related to this Privacy Policy or to exercise the above rights. Alternatively, these can be addressed via postal mail to:

Production Attorney  
Talk WW Productions, LLC  
226 W. 26th Street, 4th Floor  
New York, NY 10001

 **Date Last Modified:**

This Privacy Policy was last modified May 05, 2019.
